buypakistan.com 2012-08-15

# Privacy Policy

## Information Collection and Use

Buypakistan.com is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, e-mail address, and payment information such as your credit card number. We also require you to submit a username and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. If you elect to receive our newsletter or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items. 

## Registration

In order to process your orders placed on this website, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you will be required to provide your contact information, which includes your name, e-mail address, telephone number and street address. This information is used to provide you with important Buypakistan.com services such as automated order status updates via e-mail. 

## Order

Most of the information collected in the registration process will be used to process orders. During the order process, you will have to provide financial information such as your credit card number, expiration date, money order, wire transfer or check information. This information is used for billing purposes and to fulfill your order. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this contact information to get in touch with you. To properly process your credit card information, we must share your personal and financial information with the merchant bank for authorization and approval. This process is protected by an enhanced security system. See the Security section below for more details on security measures and procedures. We do not share your personal and financial information with any third parties, except those specified in the Sharing section of this policy. 

## Cookies

We customize certain Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. If you choose to reject the cookie, you can still browse our store but will be unable to use the shopping cart to buy merchandise. The Buypakistan.com shopping cart cannot function without cookies enabled so that the necessary information to process your order is retained. If you disable cookies, Buypakistan.com will be unable to accept your online order. We will not share any personally identifiable information provided by this cookie with any third party. We will, however, link data stored in cookies to the personally identifiable information you submitted while on our site. This allows us to personalize your shopping experience and discern user preferences to evoke subconscious feelings of familiarity and assurance. 

  * Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies.
  * This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by [Buypakistan.com](http://www.newegg.com/) only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers

## Log Files

We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. We do not link IP addresses to personally identifiable information, and we do not distribute or share IP information with any third parties. 

## Sharing

We may employ third party companies to perform functions on our behalf. These functions may include order fulfillment, package delivery, may not use it for other purposes. 

## Testimonials

The testimonials section of the Buypakistan.com website is for the purpose of sharing positive experiences. The testimonials section is moderated to ensure accurate and positive testimonials. Published testimonials are genuine and are not edited or altered by Buypakistan.com. Buypakistan.com reserves the right to post or remove any testimonial at its discretion. 

By posting your comment(s) or testimonial(s) ("Testimonial") on our website, you give us permission to reprint or use the Testimonial in connection with our business. You also are agreeing to the following: (1) The reprint or use of the Testimonial will be at our discretion and without compensation; (2) We may use the Testimonial with or without any pseudo (pen) name credit; (3) Our right to use the Testimonial is perpetual and may be assigned by us; (4) We may use the Testimonial locally, nationally or globally and such use may be made in any media, information or communication platform (including Internet advertising) currently in use or later developed; and (5) You and not someone else composed and posted the Testimonial. 

Other than your pseudo (pen) name, which we may or may not use, your personal contact information will not be disclosed in connection with our reprint or use of your Testimonial.

## Children

Buypakistan.com does not sell products for purchase by children. Youth-oriented products are sold for purchase by adults only. If you are under the age of 14, you may only use Buypakistan.com in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 13. Buypakistan.com is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children. 

## Links

This website contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Buypakistan.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this website. 

## Security

Buypakistan.com takes precautions to protect its customers' information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline. 

## Special Offers

Our special offers are sent only to customers who grant Buypakistan.com permission to send them such information. 

To honor the privacy of our users, we offer the option to not receive these types of communications. At the time of your order, you may opt to not receive special offers and news by clicking the appropriate field. Furthermore, all special offers are sent via e-mail and include an opt-out link if you no longer wish to receive special offers and news. Customers might still receive intermittent updates on products, services, specials or Buypakistan.com news. Please reference the Choice/Opt-out section below for further details on how to be removed from our mailing list should you choose to be removed. 

## Correction/Updating/Reviewing Personal Information

Customers may change or review their stored account information such as street address or e-mail address through our website.You must have your username and password in order to access your account. In the event you forget both your username and password, please contact our customer service department for assistance. 

## Choice/Opt-out

For customers who wish to opt-out and stop receiving Buypakistan.com special offers and related news, Buypakistan.com provides several ways to do so. Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by un-checking the "permission to send" field when processing their orders. They may also send e-mails to webmaster@Buypakistan.com with a request to be removed. Finally, they may use the link provided in all Buypakistan.com communications to automatically unsubscribe. 

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our homepage.
